我不想成為超級英雄
I'm not gonna be a superhero.
那你一個浩克還想干什么
What else ya gonna do as a Hulk?
我這部劇的前情提要...
Previously, on my show...
還記得我約會的那個崇拜狂嗎
Remember my date with the guy with the fetish?
你是叫我樣本嗎
Did you call me a specimen?
我是在夸你呢
As a compliment.
你應該穿盧克給你定制的 那件超級套裝
I wanna see the supersuit that Luke made you.
為什么 我才不穿
Why? I won't wear it.
你都沒告訴我 你被提名“年度女律師”了
You didn't tell me you were nominated for Female Lawyer of the Year.
咱們是不是能參加晚宴了
Do we get to go to a gala?
我朋友給我發了個鏈接 是一段發在“情報聯盟”上的視頻
My friend sent me a link to a video post on that site, Intelligencia.
干掉女浩克
-我遇到了一位男士 -我叫喬希
- I met a guy. - I'm Josh.
我們約會過幾次 進展挺順利的
We went on a few dates, it was going great.
然后我就聯系不上他了
And I haven't heard from him.
我覺得他就是不辭而別了
You were ghosted.
當你再想起喬希的時候
Next time you think of Josh,
記住我們遇到的每個人 無論他傷害你有多深
everyone we meet, no matter how much they hurt you,
都會讓你成長
is a lesson learned.
這臺的屏幕是OLED還是QLED
Is this OLED or QLED?
我在網上查到
My online research tells me
OLED的色彩分辨率和畫面質量更好
OLED is better for color resolution and picture quality.
有趣的是 我還真記住了...
Funny enough, I actually read the article...
雖然商店關門了 但是別忘了
The store might be closed, but you forgot about
看門蛙還在呢
the Guard Frog.
看門蛙是什么玩意
The hell is a Guard Frog?
這就是他的名字吧
I think it's his name.
我的名字叫跳蛙
My name is Leapfrog.
我剛才只是在特定的情況下 扮演看門蛙的角色
I'm just acting like I'm the Guard Frog in this particular instance.
“看門蛙”
"The Guard Frog"?
對 但是我的名字叫跳蛙
Yeah, but my name is Leapfrog.
明白 這點你已經反復聲明過了 帕蒂利奧先生
Yes, that has been noted several times, Mr. Patilio.
-好吧 -那么 你的戰服有質量問題...
- Cool. - So, your defective suit...
沒錯 當時這些壯漢正在圍攻我
Right. So, I was surrounded by these huge guys.
霹靂回旋跺
Twisting toe jam!
雖然敵眾我寡 但是我看得出來 他們忌憚我
Although I was outnumbered, I could tell they were afraid of me.
所以為了緩和局勢 我喊出了標志性的口號
So, in order to de-escalate the situation, I shouted my signature catchphrase.
怒蛙咆哮 全部干掉
Time to ribbit and rip it!
接下來發生的就是
And then next thing I know,
我那件耐九百度高溫的防火戰服 居然著火了
my inflammable suit with a 900-degree threshold is on fire.
結果可想而知 我的雙腿三級燒傷
And, you guessed it, I have third-degree burns all over my legs.
我需要正義的裁決
I mean, I deserve justice.
還得賠償我承受的痛苦 無論是肉體上...
And compensation for all of my pain, mental anguish and...
還是精神上
Stuff.
你這個情況確實是 非常典型的產品缺陷案件
Well, this does seem to be a pretty clear case of manufacturer's defect,
涉及產品事故 嚴格產品責任 以及違反質保
negligence, strict liability, and breach of warranty.
-對吧  -我認為
- Yes? - I do believe
你應該能獲得補償性損害賠償
you are owed compensatory damages.
太棒了
Yeah! Whoo!
制造商的名字是什么
What is the name of the manufacturer?
盧克·雅各布森 他專門做超能戰服
Luke Jacobson. He specializes in supersuits.
不是吧
Oh, shit.
雅各布森是唯一能給我這體格 做衣服的裁縫
Jacobson is the only tailor I can go to because of my unique physique.
您覺得讓巴戈接這個案子可以嗎
Do you think maybe Pug could take this one?
帕蒂利奧先生可是我們的大客戶
Mr. Patilio is one of our biggest clients.
就那個打扮成青蛙的家伙
The guy dressed as a frog?
我是說老帕蒂利奧
Mr. Patilio, Sr.
總之 絕對不能得罪 帕蒂利奧家的人
Look, it's very important that we keep the Patilios happy.
尤金本人對浩克來負責這個案件 也很興奮
Eugene is also very excited to have a Hulk on the case.
而且為了讓你接手 沃爾特斯小姐
And they're willing to sign a conflict waiver
他們愿意簽署利益沖突豁免函
to have you, Ms. Walters.
但是要我幫客戶去告雅各布森
But I believe I would be ethically compromised
我自己的立場會很不堅定的
in representing a client against Jacobson.
我喜歡那些漂亮衣服 我可不想得罪他
I like my nice clothes and I don't wanna piss him off.
你又不是第一次 處理涉及利益沖突的案子了
You've handled a client who had to sign a conflict waiver before,
更何況上次那個案子的沖突 可比這個大多了
in a case one would argue is a lot more personal than this one.
沒錯 但是我可不想 再處于那種境地了
Yes, and I would love not to be in that position again.
而且他現在正給我做晚宴禮服呢
Also, he's making me a dress for the gala.
好吧 沃爾特斯小姐
Very well, Ms. Walters.
我建議你嘗試和雅各布森先生 達成和解
I suggest that you try to come to an agreement with Mr. Jacobson
這樣就不用對簿公堂了 明白了嗎
so then a filing would not be necessary. Understood?
-怒蛙咆哮 全部干掉 -對 怒蛙咆哮 全部干掉
- Ribbit and rip it. - Yes, ribbit and rip it indeed.
珍妮佛 不要催我
Jennifer, do not rush me.
我和你說了 周五之前做不好
I told you your dress will not be ready until Friday.
你想在領獎臺上大放異彩吧
You wanna look good for your lawyer award, right?
當然 盧克 其實我今天來是因為...
Uh, yes. Well, Luke, I am here under some
一些不愉快的事
unpleasant business.
我最近接了一位客戶 他受了重傷
I have been retained by a client who suffered serious injuries
因為他在你這買的戰服 出了質量問題
due to a dysfunctional suit that you sold him.
還沒正式提告呢 我覺得咱們是不是可以達成某種...
Nothing has been filed. I think we can come to some kind of...
你說什么
Excuse me?
你膽敢質疑我
How dare you.
我這輩子從來沒做過有缺陷的戰服 我的作品是完美無瑕的
I have never made a defective suit in all my life. My work is impeccable.
當然了 我可是深有體會 而且我...
Obviously, I know that firsthand. And I...
相信我 接這案子我也是迫不得已
Trust me, I'm not happy to be doing this.
我不相信你
I'm not trusting you
你鬼鬼祟祟溜進來 在我背后捅刀子
after you just lumbered in here and stabbed me in the back.
還沒正式提告呢
Well, there's no lawsuit yet.
而且你如果愿意
And there won't be
對我客戶造成的傷害承擔責任 就不用打官司了
if you just take some responsibility for some of my client's injuries.
我做的戰服絕對沒有質量問題
I do not make suits that malfunction.
我的作品能自證清白
My work speaks for itself.
不好意思 你剛才說什么
Oh, excuse me. What did you say?
這件要和我說話 稍等
She wants to tell me something, hold on.
“女浩克不配再穿 盧克·雅各布森做的衣服了 ”
"She-Hulk will never get another suit by Luke Jacobson ever again?"
嘿 這件我可是付了全款的
Hey, I pre-paid for that!
那你就不該背叛我
Then you shouldn't have betrayed me.
你被封殺了 我要拉黑你 即刻生效
You are blocked, blacklisted and reported!
那我別無選擇了
Now, I am gonna take you down.
對 我覺得你那些丑八怪衣服 確實沒什么可選擇的
Well, I hope it's not down to wherever it is you get your ugly clothes from.
法庭上見
See you in court!
能不能...
Can you...
再見 倒霉鬼
Goodbye, tragedy.
《律師女浩克》
第一季第八集
本WEB版外掛字幕由  風吹來的那片云  雙語合并
雅各布森先生 我發現你沒有律師
Mr. Jacobson, I see you are presently without counsel.
你是要自我辯護嗎
Are you representing yourself?
自我辯護
Representing himself?
你可以開始計劃 怎么花你那筆賠償金了
Start planning how you're gonna spend all your new money.
雅各布森先生
Mr. Jacobson?
我當然不是要自我辯護 法官閣下 我又不蠢
Of course I'm not representing myself, Your Honor. I'm not a fool.
那你的律師在哪
Then where is your counsel?
在這呢
I'm here.
非常抱歉我來晚了 法官大人 找車位有點難
Apologies for the tardiness, Your Honor. I had trouble finding parking.
開玩笑的 其實是我的司機迷路了
I'm just kidding. My driver got lost.
我叫馬修·默多克
My name is Matthew Murdock.
我是雅各布森先生本案的代理律師
I'll be representing Mr. Jacobson in this case.
抱歉 我遲到了
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
首先我要申請
As a first point of order, I'd like to ask that
駁回對方律師提出的 要求被告配合提供客戶名單的動議
the motion to compel production of the defendant's client list be rejected
因為這份名單與本案無關
as it's not relevant to the litigation.
這個混蛋是誰
Who's this asshole?
法官大人 我認為這份名單 絕對與本案的案情部分
Your Honor, I believe this information to be incredibly relevant
有非常密切的關系
given the nature of the complaint.
雅克布森先生服務的其他客戶 也很有可能
There could be multiple instances of Mr. Jacobson's other clients
因服裝缺陷的問題而受過傷
sustaining injuries from faulty merchandise.
我認為沃爾特斯小姐會看到
I believe Ms. Walters will find that Mr. Jacobson's record
雅各布森先生的客戶滿意度調查 是零差評記錄
as it pertains to customer satisfaction to be spotless.
既然被告行事如此光明磊落 那為何不聽聽客戶的評價呢
If the defendant has nothing to hide, then why not hear from his clients?
你的前提假設毫無根據 嚴重侵犯個人隱私
That's an invasion of privacy based on a very shaky "what if."
這只是與產品責任相關案件中的 常規取證
This is a very common procedure in product liability lawsuits.
此類功能缺陷是否導致其他人受傷
It is material to the case whether
與本案絕對有關
this type of malfunction has affected other people.
雇用雅各布森先生做衣服
There is no inherent right to privacy
本身并不涉及個人隱私的問題
when employing Mr. Jacobson's tailoring services.
但是本案涉及的并非普通產品
We're not just talking about a product here.
雅各布森先生的工作
The very nature of Mr. Jacobson's line of work,
是為超級英雄定制戰服 必須保證匿名性
making suits exclusively for superheroes, necessitates anonymity.
我要提醒對方 《索科維亞協議》已經被廢除了
May I remind you that the Sokovia Accords have been repealed.
超級英雄選擇走進大眾的視野
Superheroes operate in the public eye.
作為公眾人物 他們必然會犧牲掉某些個人隱私
As public figures, it is assumed that there will be some loss of privacy.
我們現在討論的并不是名人
We're not talking about celebrities,
而是超級英雄 他們的對手企圖傷害他們
but superheroes who have enemies who will try to harm them,
和他們身邊的人
and people close to them.
這些人都是無辜的 卻會受到牽連
The ones who didn't ask to be a part of this life.
沃爾特斯女士自愿公開身份
Ms. Walters chose to have her identity be public,
但是她無權代替其他人做出選擇
but she can't choose for everyone else.
這不僅僅關系到個人隱私
This isn't about privacy for privacy's sake.
如果這方面信息遭到泄露 不但會讓我的客戶身敗名裂
If this information is not protected, not only would it ruin my client's career,
還會讓許多人陷入各種各樣的危險
it could put a lot of people in a lot of danger,
而這些都是因為某個人 使用戰服不當造成的
and all over one man's misuse of a suit.
我贊同默多克先生的主張
I'm in agreement with Mr. Murdock.
原告提出的配合取證的動議 不予批準
Motion to compel discovery is denied.
等等 這是說 我別想再有新戰服了
Wait. Does that mean I don't get a new suit?
先坐下
Sit down!
什么 不行...看看我這身戰服
What, no... Look at this thing!
我以后還怎么穿啊
How am I supposed to wear this?
帕蒂利奧先生 你的助推器用的是什么燃料
Mr. Patilio, what kind of fuel did you use in your boosters?
噴氣機燃料
Jet fuel.
等等 你給戰服助推器 用的是噴氣機燃料
Wait a minute, you used jet fuel in your boosters?
我的使用說明書可不是這么寫的
Because that's not what my instructions said.
什么
What?
我沒用那個
No, I didn't.
他在說謊 別問我怎么知道的 我就是知道
He's lying. Don't ask me how I know, I just know.
是的 我們都看得出來他在說謊 默多克先生
Yes, we can all tell he's lying, Mr. Murdock.
如果原告未按商家提供的說明書 正確使用戰服
If the plaintiff ignored the manufacturer's explicit instructions,
這將免除掉被告的一切責任
then the defendant is absolved of all liability.
原告的訴訟請求被駁回
I'm dismissing this case.
我會不會坐牢啊
Am I gonna go to jail?
不會 但是我巴不得送你進去
No, but I would like you to.
-盧克 -干什么 小丑
- And Luke, Luke. - Yes, clown?
我就是想向你道個歉...
I just wanted to apologize for...
因為你居然敢質疑我的手藝
For daring to question my craftsmanship?
你還能不能繼續給我做衣服
Is there any way that we could go back to you being my tailor?
珍妮佛
Jennifer, Jenny, Jen.
不能 因為我現在非常討厭你
No. Because I hate you now.
案例酒吧
什么意思
What's this?
那位先生請您的
It's from that guy over there.
蘋果馬丁尼 我喜歡
An appletini? Cute.
介意我坐過來嗎
Mind if I join you?
隨你
Sure.
幫我拿一下好嗎
Would you mind?
我是來示好的
I wanted to extend a peace offering.
我最討厭那些 占領道德制高點的人了
Ugh! I hate it when people take the high road.
所以你到底是來干什么的 馬修·默多克
So, what's your story, Matt Murdock?
你不遠萬里從紐約飛過來
You're from New York
難道就為了個產品責任的小案子
but you flew all the way out here for a product liability case?
盧克·雅各布森給我做過幾套新衣服 我欠他的人情
Luke Jacobson made a couple of new suits for me, so I owed him one.
這我倒是沒看出來
Doesn't really look like it.
貶低一個盲人的著裝 也太不體面了
That's a low blow insulting a blind man's clothes.
我穿著褲子呢 對吧
I'm wearing pants, right?
你有自己的律所 對吧
You have your own practice, right?
沃爾特斯小姐 你調查過我的底細了
Ms. Walters, have you been checking up on me?
是啊 這能怪我嗎 你忽然冒出來
Yeah. Can you blame me? You came out of nowhere
然后讓我那個蠢貨客戶
and you made my dumb client admit
當庭承認他比我想象的還要蠢
to being even dumber than I thought he was in court.
你是怎么知道噴氣機燃料的
How did you know about the jet fuel?
直覺
A hunch.
話說那家伙是什么情況
What is his deal, by the way?
-你再來直覺一次試試 -好啊
- Well, I'll give you one guess. - Okay.
和“富爸爸”有關
It rhymes with "rich parents."
等等 我把答案說出來了
Wait, I said it was rich parents.
他父親是我們的重要客戶 所以他自然也是重要客戶了
His dad is a very important client, so he is a very important client.
好吧 聽過這句話嗎  “成全別人就是成全自己”
Well, you know the expression, "One for them, one for us"?
聽過
Yeah.
我在地獄廚房執業
Well, I run my practice in Hell's Kitchen,
大部分做的都是公益訴訟 這就是“成全自己”的部分
and we mostly do pro bono work. The "us" part.
但是我時不時也會接手 一些大客戶的案子
But I do on occasion take a job with a bigger client
他們的律師費給得很到位 這就是“成全別人”的部分
when the bills start piling up. The "them" part.
馬修·默多克的隱秘雙重生活 他是怎么做到的
Wow. Secret double lives of Matt Murdock, how does he do it?
作為一個全職“成全別人”的人
As someone who works for "them" full-time,
我可真沒精力再去干別的了
I really don't have any gas in the tank for anything else.
對 你說的沒錯
Yeah, you say that,
但是你的位置很特殊 你可以去日行一善啊
but I think you're in a unique position to do some real good.
我們是同道中人
You see, the way I see it,
珍妮佛·沃爾特斯可以利用法律 幫助那些被社會辜負的人
Jen Walters can use the law to help people when society fails them.
而女浩克可以幫助那些 被法律辜負的人
And She-Hulk can help people when the law fails them.
所以 你可以的 只要你愿意...
So, you can, if you choose...
這樣就能兩全其美了
Be the best of both worlds.
-我先失陪一下 -好
- Excuse me for a moment. - Yeah.
你們都有感覺了 對吧 不會只有我吧
We're all feeling this, right, it's not just me?
托德 - 我有個法律問題 需要立刻跟你討論
晚上8點在“馬蹄花”見
還記得托德嗎 那個惡心的科技宅 女浩克的崇拜狂
Ugh! You remember Todd, that gross tech bro with the She-Hulk fetish?
嘿 想不想再喝一杯
Hey, do you wanna get another round?
珍妮佛 我很抱歉 我得走了 有正事要辦
Jen, I am so sorry, I have to go. Something has just come up with work.
沒事 能理解 我也有正事
Oh, yeah. Totally. I got work, too.
沒事
- Yeah. - Um...
好吧 遇見你真的...
Uh, yeah, it was really...
很高興遇到你
It was nice meeting you.
我也是
Yeah, you, too.
托德 - 古利庫霍律所承諾 隨時為我服務
我可以給霍利韋打電話 確認一下是不是我弄錯了
好吧
Okay.
費爾普斯先生
Mr. Phelps.
什么先生...叫我托德
Mr... It's Todd.
所以 你要和我討論 什么十萬火急的事
So, what is the urgent matter that you wanted to discuss with me?
對...我最近在拍賣會上看藝術品
Oh, yeah... So, I was at an auction recently buying art
然后收了這個 真品瓦坎達戰矛
and then, get this, they had an authentic Wakandan war spear.
我當然最后拿下了 花了一百個
So, I, of course, win the auction. A millie.
一百萬
It's a million.
-是美金 -我聽明白了
- Dollars. - I got that.
好吧 那你肯定想見識一下 對吧
Yeah. So... I mean, you gotta see it, right?
我這有照片 給你看看
So, here it is. Check this out.
砰 是不是很酷
Boom. How cool is that?
這東西現在是我的了
I mean, I own that now.
天啊 論非洲收藏品 沒人能跟我媲美了
God, no one is collecting African shit on my level.
我太喜歡了 我愛瓦坎達 知道嗎 我去那留過學
I love it. I love Wakanda. You know, I actually studied abroad there.
真的嗎
Really?
瓦坎達萬歲
Wakanda Forever!
我...這有點尷尬了
Ooh! I... That makes me uncomfortable.
你在購買過程中遇到法律問題了
So, is there a legal issue with your purchase?
沒有 不過 是的 他們想要回去
No, no. Well, okay, they want it back
因為顯然這是被殖民者偷出來的
because apparently it was stolen by colonizers,
但是關我什么事 我有購買收據
but whatever. I mean, I got the receipts.
知道嗎 聽著 寶貝
You know, listen, babe.
咱們就別藏著掖著的了 我這個人本來也不喜歡兜圈子
Let's just drop the whole coy thing 'cause I don't play games, okay?
我對你有意思 我知道你對我也有...
And I can feel it and I can tell that we're both feeling it.
沒有
Ugh! No!
再見 我會按一整個小時計費的
Goodbye. Oh, and I'm billing you for the whole hour.
什么
What?
天啊
Oh, God.
-喂  -謝天謝地 沃爾特斯小姐 我是跳蛙
- Hello? - Thank God! Ms. Walters, it's Leapfrog.
聽著 你得來救我 我覺得有人要攻擊我
Listen, you gotta help me. I think I'm being attacked.
是法律上還是現實中
Legally or physically?
當然是在現實中 但是我覺得法律上應該也有
Definitely physically. But, I mean, maybe legally, too.
你在哪
Where are you?
我正在去荷葉的路上
I'm on my way to the Lily Pad.
那是個地名嗎
Is that a place I'm supposed to know?
對 是我最有名的秘密基地
Yeah. It's my famous secret lair.
我得去找我的朋友們
Yeah, I just need to find my friends.
好的 我爭取在停車場這里甩掉他
Okay, I'm gonna try to lose him in this parking lot.
-估計會沒信號 -你離我不遠
- I'm gonna lose ya. - You're close.
我現在往你那去 咱們路上見
I'm heading to you. We'll meet in the middle.
快點
Hurry!
我的車
My car!
別多管閑事
You need to back off.
那這身戰服豈不是浪費了
And waste this outfit?
尤金 給我躲開
Eugene, get out of here.
戰服真不賴
Dope supersuit!
你會后悔的
You're making a mistake.
敢動我的客戶 后悔的是你
You made a mistake when you messed with my client!
小心我把你屁股揍開花
'Cause now I'm gonna whoop your ass.
我的屁股完好無損啊
Huh. My ass remains unwhooped.
是嗎 那我動真格的了
Yeah? Let's fix that.
怒蛙咆哮 全部干掉
Ribbit and rip it!
想往哪跑 還沒打完呢
Where are you going? We're not done.
你挺執著的呀
You're very persistent, aren't you?
你挺招人煩的
And you're very annoying.
回頭見
See you later!
來啊
Come on!
抓住你了
Gotcha.
珍妮佛
Whoa, whoa! Jen!
馬修
Matt?
等等 你不會是裝瞎吧 老兄  是的話問題可就嚴重了
Wait. Do you pretend to be blind, man? 'Cause that is really problematic.
不 我是真的看不見 冷靜一下 我...
No. No, no, I'm blind, I'm blind. Relax. I...
我利用空間感知法看見周圍的情況
I have a spatial method that I use to see.
類似回聲定位
Oh, like echolocation?
對 差不多吧 這個... 簡單來說就是我聽力超凡
Yeah, kind of. It's... Basically I have really good hearing.
至少曾經是
Or at least I did.
等等 你為什么要襲擊我的客戶
Wait, why were you attacking my client?
跳蛙才是幕后黑手
Leapfrog is the bad guy here.
他綁架了盧克·雅各布森 拿他當人質
He kidnapped Luke Jacobson. He's holding him hostage.
那我們開打之前你怎么不告訴我
Why didn't you tell me that before we fought?
你要把我屁股揍開花之前怎么不問我
Why didn't you ask me before trying to whoop my ass?
對不起 我把穿得像惡魔的人 直接當成壞人了
I'm sorry that I assumed the guy dressed as the devil was the bad one.
這個理由挺充分的
Yeah, that's a fair point.
那么你也是超級英雄嗎
So, are you, like, a superhero?
比如說金惡魔
Like the Gold Devil?
我是夜魔俠
I'm Daredevil.
番茄醬和芥末醬的配色 確實挺大膽啊
It is very daring to use ketchup and mustard as your color scheme.
要幫你轉達盧克嗎
How 'bout I tell Luke?
不要 千萬別
No! No, please don't.
好吧 要是你取笑夠了 我得去你的客戶那救我的客戶了
Okay. Well, if you're done making fun, I need to save my client from your client.
好吧 咱們走吧
Okay, yeah, let's go.
你之前砸過停車場嗎
You ever destroy a parking lot before?
糟糕 我去留個紙條
Crap. I'll go leave a note.
荷葉
夠隱蔽的
Hmm. Subtle.
第二版的話 咱們可得把真本事全用上
For version two, we gotta go all out.
加一個防彈盾牌
I'm talking bulletproof shields,
內置英國口音實時互動的人工智能
fancy AI with a British voice that talks to you.
對了 再來幾只毒飛鏢 用樹蛙的造型
Oh, snap! And some of those poison darts, like the tree frogs.
我不知道是誰告訴你 你能駕馭得了這種配色
I don't know who told you that you could pull off this color,
但是你應該去找他們 然后斃了他們
but you should go back to them and shoot them.
我說 你被我綁來這里 肯定對我很不爽
Look, I know you're just being mean because I kidnapped you,
但是多少積點口德 哥們
but words hurt, man.
弟兄們 你們覺得“彈跳小隊” 這個名字怎么樣
Guys, what do we think about the name "Leap Squad"?
就叫“彈跳小隊”
You know, like, "Leap Squad!"
這種蠢貨居然也有跟班
I can't believe this dodo has henchmen.
其實這不奇怪 我敢賭這幫打手都是替他爸賣命的
Actually, I can. I bet these goons work for his dad.
不對 你完全弄錯了
Nah, see, that's where you're wrong.
跟班和打手是截然不同的兩類人
Goons and henchmen are two completely different animals.
跟班認為他們是在搞事業 而打手只是來掙錢的
Henchmen believe in the cause, goons are just there for the paycheck.
跟班 打手 隨便吧
Henchmen, goons, whatever.
這棟樓里有二十五個打手
There are 25 goons in the building.
樓下七個 樓上八個 還有十個在走廊
Seven below us, eight in the front, and 10 in the hallway.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
我能聽見他們的心跳
I can hear their heartbeats.
你能聽到他們的心跳  得了吧 這有點太扯了
You can hear their heartbeats? Come on, that's a little far-fetched.
我也能聽見你的 你的心跳有點快啊
I can hear yours, too. Your heart's beating pretty fast.
什么
What?
什么 不 才沒有 我心臟好著呢
What? No, it's not. I'm healthy.
好吧
Okay.
我先潛入進去 搞定后面那幾個
I'll sneak in and take out the goons in the back.
一個差不多十五秒吧
It'll take me 15 seconds for each one.
我去把那十個都解決了 你在這等我
So, wait here until I've gotten all 10.
我可不想在這等上半個小時 看著你把他們挨個干掉
I'm not gonna sit here for half an hour while you pick off goons one by one.
你數學這么差啊
That's not how that math works out.
我可是個浩克 干嗎不讓我一路砸過去
I'm a Hulk. How about I just smash our way in?
可是他們有槍 珍妮佛
They have weapons, Jennifer.
巧了 女浩克正好是刀槍不入的 馬修
Yeah, good thing She-Hulk is indestructible, Matthew.
潛入才是上策 我干過無數次了
Stealth's the way to go. I've done this a million times.
你闖進過全是暴徒的倉庫嗎
Have you broken into a warehouse full of goons?
那你告訴我咱倆誰有超能力
Remind me again who has the superpowers here?
我是指著自己問的
I'm pointing at myself.
對 我知道 我會回聲定位 忘了嗎
Oh, yeah, I know. I have echolocation, remember?
讓我先把正事干了
Just let me do my thing.
好 那我也去忙了
Yeah, and I will do my thing.
你...你沒什么可忙的吧 你根本就沒經驗
You... You don't have a thing. You don't ever do this.
聽我指揮就行
Just follow my lead.
好吧 這樣也挺好
Okay, I guess that's pretty cool.
我想說 我尊重你打扮成青蛙的想法
So, I said I respect that you wanna dress up like a frog,
但是這不代表我想當只小蛙仔啊
but that doesn't mean I'm cool with being a baby frog.
等等 他是想讓咱們當“蝌蚪”吧
Wait, I thought he wanted to call us "Tadpoles."
沒錯 哥們
Yeah, man.
你怎么連青蛙幼崽都不知道...
How do you not know what...
蝌蚪五號 請講
GOON 2 ON WALKIE: Tadpole five, come in.
后門這邊需要增援 我們被...
We need backup at the rear entrance. We got...
蝌蚪五號 請重復
Tadpole five, repeat.
頂住 增援馬上就到
Hang tight, backup's on the way.
女浩克暴擊
She-Hulk smash.
還有這么多跟班和打手
Ugh! More hench-goons?
要不散伙算了
How about we don't?
嘿 那可是古董
Whoa! Hey! That's vintage!
嘿 你在干什么 你應該幫我才對
Hey, what are you doing? You're supposed to be helping me.
我就是在幫你啊 我在阻止你惹出更大的麻煩
I am helping you. I'm stopping you from getting into even more trouble.
去報警
Go call the police.
別沖我嚷嚷 我已經被嚇得夠嗆了
Don't you yell at me. I'm already very stressed out.
尤金 我給你點專業意見吧
Eugene, let me give you some legal advice.
在你還沒犯下更重的罪之前 立刻停手
Stop now, before you rack up even more serious charges.
法律層面上 我們可以用狂躁癥作為借口
Legally speaking, we could say this is an episode of mania...
暫時性精神錯亂很難證明 但是你這個策略還不錯
Temporary insanity is murky, but it's not a bad strategy.
我更傾向于歸咎為因未確診的 創傷后遺癥導致的應激障礙行為
I'd angle this more as a form of traumatic expression due to undiagnosed PTSD.
所以這個惡魔忍者也是個律師
So, the devil ninja guy, he's a lawyer?
不是 就是喜歡看律政題材電視劇
No. I'm just a big fan of legal dramas.
這話我可太愛聽了
This guy's really kinda doing it for me.
你居然以為這玩意能對付我
It's sad that you thought that would work.
以退為進知道嗎
No shame in retreat.
怒蛙咆哮 全部干掉
Ribbit and rip it! Oh!
好吧 看來這下我們扯平了 那我就原諒你吧
Well, well, well, I suppose we're even now. You're forgiven.
那你會給我做晚宴禮服嗎
So, you'll make my gala dress?
當然了 我又不是冷血動物
Yes, of course. I'm not a monster.
這段時間記得控制體型
Try not to get too bloated between now and then.
真高興和那個又專業又刻薄的人 重歸于好啦
Great to be strained professional acquaintances again.
你要去給警察做份筆錄嗎
Are you gonna give a statement to the cops?
我這種人一向都是繞著警察走的
I'm not really a stick around and talk to the cops kinda guy.
積怨挺深啊
Oh, so brooding.
主要和我的秘密身份有關 你不會懂的
More of a secret identity thing. - You wouldn't understand.
今天的這一切 多虧你的幫助
Thanks for your help with all of this.
也謝謝你的幫助
Thanks for your help.
不 主要還是你的功勞
No. You're the one who helped me.
不 我只是帶頭的超級英雄而已
No. I was the lead superhero on this.
你才是那個花了半小時
Uh, you were they guy who wanted to spend half an hour
挨個解決打手們的男人
picking off each goon, one by one.
那你就是那個 造成嚴重財物損壞的女人
You were the woman who caused excessive property damage.
而且到現在也沒算明白數
And you still can't get that math right.
你什么時候回紐約
When do you head to New York?
明天
- Tomorrow. - Oh... Well...
嘿 也許下次我過來的時候 可以請你吃個飯
Hey, maybe next time I'm in town, I can take you out to dinner.
好啊 沒準也可以省略掉那些環節 直接...
Yeah, or maybe we can skip all of that and just...
別管它 沒事的
That's all right. That's okay.
等等 你是不是得...好了 來吧
Wait, you have to... All right, here you go.
好 來吧
Okay. Let's go.
早上好
Good morning.
真奇怪 你們居然還在
It's weird you guys are still here.
本集不是應該到這就結束了嗎
Doesn't it feel like this episode should be over?
你好
Hello! Uh...
你怎么不接我電話  我還以為你死了
Why didn't you answer my calls? I thought that you were dead.
然后我得破門而入呢 對了
I had to break and enter. By the way,
外面有個男的 穿著一身惡魔的戲服
there's some guy outside dressed in a devil costume
看他那模樣就知道他昨天晚上...
and he's doing the walk of shame 'cause he's...
是你...和那個...
Oh. You did... With the...
對
Yes.
好吧 感覺挺好
Oh, all right. And we're happy?
-感覺很好 -好吧
- Oh, we're happy. - Okay.
好吧 你這個小惡魔
All right. You're the devil.
說真的 這場戲是干什么的
Seriously, what is this scene?
這集已經圓滿結束了 相信我
This episode already came to a very satisfying conclusion. Trust me.
快點 咱們該走了 晚點再給我講
Come on! We gotta go. Tell me about it later.
得先把你的發型和化妝搞定 盧克給你做的禮服在哪
We have to do your hair and your makeup. Where is the gown from Luke?
晚宴禮服嗎
Oh, for the gala?
等等 這就要拍晚宴了  感覺有點不對吧
Wait, we're doing the gala? That doesn't feel right.
下一集不是大結局嗎
Is next episode the finale?
快點 走吧
Come on. Let's go.
感覺好像是在本季結束前 狗尾續貂地加一段戲
Just like a tacked-on set piece near the end of the season.
不會是要來個劇情大反轉吧  可問題是
This is the big twist, isn't it? But the question is,
是什么樣的反轉呢
is it the kind of twist that's like,
比如 “又出現了一個浩克 但是這次是紅色的”
"There's another Hulk, but this one's red,"
再比如 “把我寫死了 ”
or like, "I'm getting fridged?"
保證讓你大放異彩
We gotta make you look amazing.
我無所謂 重在參與
Whatever. I'm game.
親愛的 你怎么不帶個外套  萬一著涼了怎么辦
Sweetheart. You didn't bring a jacket? What if you get cold?
她可以穿我的 伊萊恩 我們真為你感到驕傲
She can wear mine, Elaine. We are so proud of you.
-謝謝你 老爸 -你的外套她穿不下 莫里斯
- Thank you, Dad. - Your jacket won't fit her, Morris.
絕對不能把盧克·雅各布森的 祖海·慕拉系列遮住
You can't cover up a Luke Jacobson-Zuhair Murad collaboration.
-妮基 -這名字可真拗口
Nikki! That's certainly a mouthful.
我有點緊張
I'm a little nervous.
好啦 咱們去里面坐吧
Okay. Let's find our table.
-對 他來了 你好 -咱們走吧 來吧
- Yeah. There he is. Hi! - Let's go. Come on.
來吧
Come on.
南加州法律頒獎典禮 年度女律師
智慧
Educated.
進取
Accomplished.
美麗
Beautiful.
她們在法律舞臺上展示風采 一往無前
And doing everything regular lawyers do, except backwards,
而且穿著高跟鞋
and in high heels.
今年的年度女律師得獎者是...
This year's Female Lawyer of the Year award goes to...
“女浩克”珍妮佛·沃爾特斯
Jennifer "She-Hulk" Walters!
太棒了
Let's go!
卡拉·亨特
Kara Hunter.
艾麗斯·陳
Alice Chen.
喬安妮·托里斯
Joanne Torres.
芭芭拉·韋爾斯
Barbara Wells.
馬洛里·布克
Mallory Book.
和我們分享一下 身為一名女律師有何感受
Now tell us, what's it like being a female lawyer?
獨一無二又充滿力量 感覺棒極了
So special and empowering. I love it.
吃雙份的苦 名氣是別人的一半
Twice the work, half the recognition,
還總有人問你 作為一名女性律師有何感受
and you're constantly being asked what it's like being a female lawyer.
說得好
Yeah.
其實我想借此機會感謝我的父母
I'd actually like to take this time to thank my parents.
我的朋友 以及我敬重的同事們
And my friends, and my esteemed colleagues
沒有他們 今天我就不可能站在這里
without whom I wouldn't be here today.
各位想見識一下真實的女浩克嗎
Do you want to see who She-Hulk really is?
我的身份也不算是什么秘密
Uh, my identity is not a secret.
麥克風沒聲音了
This is busted.
讓“情報聯盟”為各位揭開真相吧
This is the truth presented by Intelligencia.
女浩克不配得到你們的關注 也不配享受你們的贊美
She-Hulk does not deserve your attention. She does not deserve your praise.
更不配擁有從浩克那里 竊取的超能力
She does not deserve the power she stole from the Hulk.
這是什么東西 有誰能關掉它嗎
What the hell this? Can somebody cut this off?
能把它先關掉嗎 拜托
Can we turn this off, please?
好吧 能不能...誰能把它關掉
Okay, let's... Can we stop this?
-她就是個蕩婦 -你能先關掉嗎
- And she's a slut. - Can you stop it?
對 也許你應該躺下
Yeah, maybe you should lie down.
打擾一下 你能把這個關掉嗎
Excuse me! Can you turn this off?
別沖動 珍妮佛
Don't do it, Jen.
別沖動
Don't do it.
威爾希爾宴會廳
不許動
Don't move!
珍妮佛 不要
Jen! No!
根據漫威漫畫改編
瓦坎達
出價
珍妮佛·沃爾特斯 又名 “女浩克”
漫威影業出品
《律師女浩克》
字幕翻譯: 蟲二